http://www.doctoroogle.com/help/

Privacy Policy for our Kids Applications
We take kids privacy very seriously!
This Privacy Policy describes the information collected by DR.Oogle Inc through our kid mobile applications.
We don’t collect any personal data with our kid applications.
We don’t require you to provide any information when using our kid’s apps and we don’t collect, share or use any information about you or your device.
If you submit a support request via e-mail, we may receive your email address and other information you provide related to your support request. We use these information only to provide support to you. We don’t share your email address unless we have your express consent.
Our kids apps don’t use or collect a user’s precise geographic location.
Our kids apps don’t contain any advertising banners, but they may contain information about our other apps with links to those apps.
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us here.
×
Thanks for adding your like!
and Privacy Policy.
and Privacy Policy.
and Privacy Policy.
and Privacy Policy.
×
Login with email
Your Email Address
Enter Password
Login as:
Patient
Dentist
Submit
Forgot your password?
By signing in you agree to our Terms
and Privacy Policy.
×
Enter email to reset your password
Success! An email with reset instructions has been sent to your email address.
Doing this you agree to our Terms
and Privacy Policy.
and Privacy Policy.
×
Sorry, location not found
×
Are you sure you wish to cancel your review?
No
Yes
Welcome to DR.Oogle!
(Please update your bookmarks)
Welcome to DR.Oogle!
